### Joshua Budrow Software Engineer

Cell: (404) 518-6204

Email: JBudrowd3@gmail.com Linkedin.com/in/jbudrow Github.com/jbudrow

#### SUMMARY

New wave software engineer offering two years of experience in the full software development lifecycle – front concept through of next-generation applications and customizable solutions. Aim to build systems that are performant, scalable, secure and maintainable.

#### COMPUTER SKILLS

#### Languages

- Proficient in: Ruby on Rails, Haml/HTML, CSS
- · Familiar with: Javascript/jQuery

### **Technologies**

- Databases: Postgres, MySQL, Sqlite3
- Tools: Rspec, Cucumber, Git, TravisCI, Datadog
- · Platforms: Heroku, Amazon Web Services

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Support Engineer**

August 2016 - Present

BioIQ, Inc.

- Provide internal support for the products and services for well-known health service partners. Respond to incoming requests for support and drive informed and timely solutions.
- Queried databases and created customized reports and procedures for management and clients.
- Daily SaaS implementations for the healthcare and enterprise platforms.
- Focused on building relationships with team members, client managers, and outside vendors, with a
  focus on providing excellent customer service.

## Software Engineer

February 2016 - May 2016

The Iron Yard

- Twelve-week immersion code boot camp. Curriculum including but not limited to Ruby on Rails, data analysis, object-oriented principles, test-driven and agile development.
- Partook in daily extra-credit assignments and Ruby meet-ups monthly.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Gordon State College**

August 2011 – November 2011

Barnesville, Georgia

Humanities Major (Twelve credit hours)

## NOTABLE PROJECTS

# Votr (2016 Civic Innovation Hackathon; 4th place)

April 2016

- Forty-eight hour collaborative computer programming event, project ideas provided by the engineering team, SolTech Inc.
- Web application test case of a real-time online polling place. Votes are cast securely and displayed live in a dashboard using the Chart.js library as they come.